(Leonard:)She could have
any guy she wants.
(Leonard:)Which is probably why
(Leonard:)it took her so many years
to tell me she loved me.
(Mandy:)Maybe you should talk
to a therapist about this.
(Leonard:)Too expensive.
(Leonard:)You'd think I'd be used to women
withholding their love.
(Leonard:)I mean, my mother did.
(Leonard:)I mean, no matter
how hard I tried,
(Leonard:)she just didn't have
any interest in me.
(Mandy:)Imagine that.
(Leonard:)I wonder if that's why I have
(Leonard:)such a dysfunctional
relationship with Sheldon.
(Leonard:)I had a dream
(Leonard:)the other night that
I was in a cave
(Leonard:)and I was nursing a baby,
(Leonard:)but the baby
had Sheldon's head on it.
(Mandy:)And your wife is worried
about me?
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Hey, Leonard!
(Raj:)When you're done,
(Raj:)we came up with
a bunch more.
(Sheldon(on screen):)Then the Czech Republic
says to Slovakia,
"I don't think you understand
how being broken up works!"
(Sheldon(on screen):)Can you believe that?